欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内 字幕广告招租 商业合作Q:1585235535
你确定可以回去上班了吗 卡尔文
Are you sure you're ready to go back to work, Calvin?
都两周了 蒂娜 我膝盖早就好了 好吗
It's been two weeks, Tina. My knee is healed, all right?
当年取胆结石
I didn't stay home this long
都没跟家待这么久
when I had gallstones taken out.
你取的不是胆结石
You didn't have gallstones taken out.
是割的阑尾
It was your appendix.
反正拿东西出来了 而且我转眼就下地走路了
Well, something came out, and I was right back on my feet.
好呀 卡尔文
AlI right, Calvin.
要开启冒险征程了
Venturing out in the world?
他的征程应该是去做康复
He's supposed to be venturing to physical therapy,
可他就是不肯预约
but he won't make an appointment.
用不着 蒂娜 我可是60年代出生的
I don't need it, Tina. I was born in the 60s.
那时候啥东西都用料扎实
That's when things were built tough.
我可不像现在这帮新人
Im not made of fiberglass and plastic
是拿玻璃纤维和塑料做的
like these new people.
你好
Hi.
嘿 这个大温度计是干嘛的
Hey, what's...Hey, what's with the big thermometer?
要拿去我们筹款活动上用
It's for our fundraising campaign,
可我不能把它留在学校
but I can't leave it at school.
一些有创造力的小艺术家一直往上添砖加瓦
Some creative young artist keeps adding things to it
搞得它看起来像是别的东西
that, uh, make it look like something else.
像是什么东西
Oh. Like what?
懂了 懂了 懂了
Oh...yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
我们筹款想建一个水上中心
We're raising money to build an aquatjq center
好吸引新家庭来孛校
to attract new families to the school.
终于 我们可以对那些橡树岭学院
Finally, we can stick it to those snobs
的势利小人出口气了
at the Oak Ridge Academy.
嘿 你们知道吗 他们的自助餐厅有米其林星级哎
Hey, do you know their cafeteria has a Michelin star?
不许再在ins上关注那所学校了
Stop following that school on Insiagram!
-我该走了  -是 我也得走了
I got to run. Yeah, you know what, me too.
行吧
TINA: Okay.
够了 卡尔文
Enough, Calvin.
我给你约去做康复
I'm making you an appointment for PT.
我认识个很不错的康复师
Ooh, you know, I know a great physical therapist.
我经常会把他推荐给退伍军人事务部的人
I refer people to him at the VA all the time.
他叫德里克·弗莱
His name is Derrick Frye.
那个德里克·弗莱
Oh, theDerrick Frye?
曾经效力于公羊队的那位
Used to play for the Rams?
你听说过他
So, you've heard of him?
当然了 戴夫 我可是个爷们
Yes, Dave. I'm a man.
是看橄榄球的
And I watch football.
太好了 所以你会去做喽
Oh, good. So, you'll do it?
去 会去 如果我
Yeah. Yeah, I guess, you know, if I-
如果我真有这个需要的话
I mean, if I need to do it,
那我最好找个跟我一样
then I might as well go to someone
从事过优秀运动员的人
who's used to working on elite athletes like myself.
走了啊二位
I'm out of here, guys.
欢迎来到街区欢迎来到社区
♪ Welcome to the block, welcome to the neighborhood ♪
欢迎跟我做邻居
♪Welcome to the hood.
你怎么了这是
Whoa. What happened to you?
课后艺术俱乐部 这就是怎么了
After- school art club. That's what happened to me.
我可是历史老师 看看这上衣
I'm a history teacher. Look at this top.
我还想退货呢
I was gonna take this backl
你算运气好的了
You're lucky.
我们亲爱的校长让我指导
Our dear principal made me supervise
垒球队
the softball team.
我只能戴上那种硕大皮手套
I had to wear this huge leather glove thing.
而且还不是新的
And it was not new.
一切都是为了孩子 对吧
Well, it's all for the kids, right?
孩子会退我59块钱吗
Are the kids gonna refund me my$59?
59块 美元吗
$59? American dollars?
我报的可是原价
I'm quoting the original price.
重点是
Look, the point is,
我们工作超负荷了
we are being overworked.
我知道她是你朋友
I know she's your friend and all,
但约翰逊校长真的不能再让我们
but Principal Johnson needs to stop asking us
做双份工了
to do double duty.
她得雇几个助教
She's got to hire some teachers' aides.
听我说 没人比珍玛更关心
Look, look, no one cares about this school
这所学校了好吗
more than Gemma, okay?
她也很努力的
She busts her butt, too.
就别再对她吹毛求疵的了好吗
Let's cut her a little slack, okay?
-老师们好呀  -嘿
Hello, teacherslHey.
看起来某人的艺术课玩的很开心嘛
Oh! Looks like someone had fun in art.
那必须的
Sure did.
你知道我这人啦 愿意为孩子们做任何事
You know me, anything for the kids.
没错
That's right.
说到这个 明天下午有人有空吗
Speaking of which, is anyone free tomorrow afternoon?
谢谢 蒂娜
Thank you, Tinal
什么 我没说有空啊
Wh- wh- what? I didn't say yes.
但事出紧急
But it's an emergency.
我得有人陪同五年级学生去艾塔迪那
I need someone to chaperone the fifth graders' field trip
废物处理中心做校外实践
to the Altadena Waste Disposal Center.
你是说垃圾场
You mean the dump.
请别叫那里“垃圾场“
Please don't call it"the dump
垃圾场的人会很不满的
The dump people get very offended.
我本来要去的 可太忙了
I'd do it, but I'm swamped.
我得筹办筹款活动
I've got the fundraising campaign,
完成年度报告
the annual report to finish,
还有一连串的捐赠晚宴
back- to- back donor dinners...
再说 会很有意思的
Plus, it'll be fun.
行吧
Fine.
你最好了
You're the best
玩得开心哦 蒂娜
Have fun, Tina Mm hmm.
希望你打过破伤风疫苗了
Hope you had your tetanus shot.
你知道
Yeah, you know,
当年我是一名跑卫
I was a running back back in my day.
差点就成职业选手了
And I almost made the pros,
但是 就没通过选拔
but, you know, just missed the cut, man.
是嘛 你在哪所大学打球的
Really? What college did you play for?
就 大学也是
You know in college, too.
我没考上
I- I missed the cut.
就差那么一点点
I missed the cut.
但 我高中 初中和儿童组比赛
But, uh, I dominated in high school,
都风光无两
middle school, peewee, you know.
能跟圈内人士
It's just good to talk to somebody else
聊聊天感觉就很好
that played the game.
你知道的
You know.
好 卡尔文 我得了解下
AlI right, Calvin, I need to know,
你是受伤了还是只是有点疼
are you injured or are you hurt?
有什么区别
What's the difference?
如果你受伤了 就没法打球了
If you're injured, you can't play.
但如果你就是疼 那我会让你
But if you're hurt, I'm gonna put your butt
重回球场 还把球给你
back on the field and give you the ball.
好吧
Okay...Mm- hmm.
现在 我再问你一次
Now, I'm gonna ask you one more damn time- -
你是受伤了还是只是有点疼
Are you injured or are you hurt?
我还是有点不明白
You know, I'm still a little confused
但我该说 有点疼
...but I'm gonna say"hurt"?
这才像样嘛
Now we're talking.
-现在我们让你从替补席上起来  -好
Now let's get you off that bench...Okay.
-然后重回球场  -好的
and back in the game. All right.
这个电刺激机器
Now, this electro stim machine
会让血液流向
is gonna get the blood flowing
你的膝盖
to your knee.
-我们开始吧  -好的
Let's get to work All right.
感觉如何
How's that feel?
都觉不出它开了
: I didn't even know it was on.
这才对嘛
That's what I'm talking about.
那就来调大功率
Let's crank it up, then.
好
Okay.
一份耕耘 一份收获
No pain, no gain.
这是我的座右铭
That's my motto.
好
AlI right.
现在有起色了
Now we re getting somewhere.
你还好吗
You good?
挺好 很不错
: I'm okay. I'm all right.
好了兄弟
Whoo. Okay, man.
谢谢你能来 哥们
Well, thanks for coming, man.
这次疗程很不错
That was a good one right there.
你是觉得我们这就完事了吗
Are you under the impression that we're done here?
不是 先生
No, sir.
教练 老师 医生 医生
Coach...sir...D- doctor. Doctor?
-选一个  -好哒
Pick onel Okay.
好 就是说 爸今天一路开车去上班
Right. So, Pop drove all the way to work today
却没从车里出来
but didn't get out of his truck?
我觉得他膝盖还在疼
I think his knee still hurts.
我们不得不在停车场召开员工会议
We had to have our staff meeting in the parking lot.
要有他不喜欢的想法 他就会按喇叭
Whenever he didn't like an idea, he just honked.
我该走了
Ooh. I'd better go.
我上课要迟到了
I am about to be late for class.
好
Uh, okay.
马尔科姆 嗯 我有东西要给你看
Malcolm, yeah, I got something to show you, man.
关于你女
It's about your girl-
-什么  -珍妮尔
What? Janelle!
嘿 近来可好
Hey, how you doing?
你背那个电脑包酷毙了
You're rocking that computer bag.
谢谢
Thank you.
好
Okay.
-拜 宝儿  -拜
Bye, babe, Bye.
回见
See you later.
什么情况 特雷
Uh...what's going on, Trey?
行吧 是这样 我就有话直说了
AII right, look, I'm not even gonna sugarcoat this.
刚才我刷探探 想找个媳妇
I was scrolling on Tinder, looking for a wife- -
找你媳妇还是别人家媳妇
Yours or someone else's?
我是很开放的
I mean, Im open.
言归正传 我刷到了珍妮尔
Anyway, I swiped on Janelle.
珍妮尔
Whoa, Janelle?
你为什么会刷到我的珍妮尔
Why would you swipe on my Janelle?
不是 我只是在刷着玩
Nah, see, I was just swiping and swiping,
都差点没发现是她
and before I realized, it it was her.
而且你不能取消配对
And you can't un- swipe.
她为啥要上约会软件
Why is she on a dating app?
我不知道 但不管你做什么
I don't know, but whatever you do,
别说是我告诉你的 我不想当告密的
don't tell her I told you, 'cause I ain't no snitch.
-放心 兄弟  -别这么说
I got you, man. Don't say that.
嘿 我忘带钥匙了
Hey. I forgot my keys.
是啊 特雷在探探上刷到你了
Yeah, uh, Trey saw you on Tinderl
不 我没有 真没有
No, I didn't. No, I didn't
拜托 特雷
Come on, Trey.
没错
Yes.
软件我是没删
I guess I still have the app,
但我不会打开看
but I wouldn't say I'm onthere.
比如《愤怒的小鸟》我也没删
I mean, I still have Angry Birds.
不过 我确实得给自己腾出点储存空间
Yeah, I guess I need to free up some storage space.
是个好主意
Yeah, that's, that's a great idea.
不如就先把探探删了
Why don't you start with Tinder?
对啊 得腾出空间给我们的照片啊
I mean, I need more space for our pictures.
-还有那个视频  -小声点
And that video Shh.
哟呵
BOTH: Damn!
怎么了
What?
我是说
Well, I mean,
你终于安定下来了
you- you're finally settling down.
安定下来 你说啥呢
Oh, settling down? What you talking about?
你让她删掉了约会软件
I mean, you made her delete her dating app.
这相当于低调求婚了
You low- key just proposed.
什么 太可笑了吧
What? That's ridiculous, man.
-马尔科姆有女朋友了  -够了 停
JMalcolm's got a girlfriend! JAlI right, stop.
-别这样 谁都能  -马尔科姆有女朋友了
Stop. Anybody can J Malcolm's got a girlfriend, Malcolm's got a girlfriend. f
冰箱里好像有东西坏了
I think there's something rotten in the fridge.
不是冰箱里的味儿
It's not the fridge.
没错 是我
Yes, it's me!
有个孩子以为在垃圾堆里看到一张
One of the kids thought he saw a hundred dollar bill
百元大钞 非要下去拾
in a pile of garbage and went after it.
猜猜是谁把他拉出来的 我
And guess who had to pull him out? Mel
后来发现是张脱衣舞俱乐部的传单
Turned out to be a flyer for a strip club.
向帕萨迪纳最棒的老师问好了
Hello to the best faculty in all of Pasadena.
哦我去 这里味儿真冲
Ooh, it's a little ripe in here.
那是因为我刚从
That's because I just got back
你发配我去的“废物处理中心”回来
from that "waste treatment center" that you sent me to.
天 感激不尽
Ugh, thank you so much.
我想给你个拥抱 但是吧
I'd hug you, but...you know.
好了
Now.
谁有红色的马克笔
Who has a red marker?
我有个振奋人心的好消息
I have exciting news.
这袋子下面的东西跟我想的一样吗
Is that bag covering what I think it's covering?
我都把它锁柜子里了
It was in a locked cabinet.
也不知这些孩子是怎么拿到的
I don't know how these kids are getting to it.
是家长干的 找他们家长算账
It's the parents. I blame the parents.
但不是当着他们面算 因为
But not to their faces, because.
新水上运动中心已经完成
we are now at 85%of our fundraising goal
了85%的筹款
for the new aquatic center.
我们学校的招生手册一定会很好看的
It's gonna look so great on the school's brochure.
对了 瑞安老师 你要帮我
Oh, Mr. Ryan, I need you
设计一本小册子
to design a brochure.
同时我还要搞辩论俱乐部
On top of dlebate club,
停车场值班和模拟联合国吗
parking lot duty, and ModelU. N. ?
太感谢了 你真能干
Thank youl You aree rock star.
你们为孩子们如此加班加点
I really can't thank you all enough
真不知该怎么感谢你们
for going thejextra mile for our kids.
你要是真想感谢我们
You- you really want to thank us?
就雇几个助教
Try hirjng some teachers' aides.
这的确是个好主意
That would be fantastic.
但我恐怕我们预算不够
I wish we could afford it.
哦 我得跑去参加
Oops! Ive got to run
无声拍卖的筹备会了
to an organizing meeting for the silent auction.
待会儿再闻你
Smell you later.
抱歉 我就想玩个梗
Sorry, that's just an expression.
来吧 卡尔文 开始吧
Now come on, Calvin. Let's go.
我干这个是出了名的
I've got a reputation here.
在第二或第三次复健时
By the second or third session,
我能让客户恢复到50%
I've always gotten my client to 50%.
没人能打败我
I'm undefeated.
在复健方面吗
At therapy?
整个人生方面
At life.
好了 我们现在来拔火罐
Now, we're gonna do some fire cupping.
你不介意温度高一点吧
You don't mind a little heat, do you?
我介意被烧死
Well, I mind being set on fire.
一点小火苗而已啦
A little fire never hurt anybody.
才不是呢
Well, that's not true.
不然医院也不会有烧伤科
That's why they have burn units.
嘿 卡尔文
Ooh, hey, Calvin
抱歉 抱歉
Sorry, sorry.
我不想打扰你们哈
I don't want to interrupt.
哦哦 没打扰
Oh, oh, it's not interrupting.
根本没打扰到我们
You're not interrupting.
我永远会为戴夫腾出时间
There's always time for Dave. You know what?
拔火罐的事儿就先到这儿吧
Uh, let's put a pin in this fire cup thing, okay?
好吧
Okay.
你都进行到拔火罐这一项了
Is it fire cupping time?
我还记得德里克给我拔火罐的时候
You know, I remember when Derek did this to me.
是挺疼的
It was rough.
是吗
It was?
我都被你骗过了
You could have fooled me.
嘿 你这个哥们儿戴夫
Hey, your man Dave, here?
他是真不怕疼
He can take some pain.
就他
This Dave?
休闲风的戴夫
Fanny pack Dave?
哦 没错
Oh, yeah.
这家伙超硬汉的
This man s a beast.
除了巨石强森 我就没见过
I haven't worked with a guy this tough
这么厉害的人
since The Rock.
好吧
: Okay,
你是要把戴夫比作巨石强森吗
did you just compare Dave to The Rock?
不不
Oh, no,
我是把巨石比作戴夫
I compared The Rock to Dave.
卡尔文 听着 别被德里克
Now, now, Calvin, look, I don't want
的溢美之词搞得自愧不如
Derek's effusive compliments to make you feel less than.
好吧 不是每个人都有我的力量和毅力
Okay? Not everyone has my strength and fortitude.
嗯哼
Mm- hmm.
你拧个瓶盖都要我帮忙
I have to open jars for you.
你知道吗
You know what?
来来来 给我点上
Come on. Light me back on fire.
咱们开始吧
Let's go!
所以蒂娜和其他老师
So Tina and the teachers
让你雇助教
asked you to hire teachers'aides?
是的
Yeah.
你却送她们蜡烛和
So you're giving them candles
好时之吻
and Hersheyls kisses?
我们又买不起高档货
We can't afford the good stuff.
这是开市客之吻
These are Costco Smooches.
嗯 那个是
And, uh, that's
没错 是毛 戴夫
Yes, it's hair, Dave.
他们还画上了毛
They've added hair.
这个艺术家越来越大胆了
The artist has gotten ambitious.
希望这些举动能赢得老师的好感
I just hope the teachers appreciate this gesture.
我不知道还能做什么
I don't know what else to do.
他们就是不理解
They just don't understand
水上运动中心会为学校带来多大收益
what the aquatic center will do for the school.
其实我也不理解
I mean, I don't, either.
我朋友没一个理解的
None of my friends do.
还好
Well, luckily,
你朋友不是学校校长
your friends don't run the school.
嘿 伙计
Hey, buddy, Is that
你手上的是马克笔吗
Is that Magic Marker on your hand?
呃 我不知道 怎么就出现在我口袋里
Uh, I don't know. They're in my pockets.
我温度计上的睾丸原来是你画的
Were you the one drawing testicles on my thermometer?
珍玛 别激动 咱儿子绝不会这么做
Okay, Gemma, relax Our son would never do that.
那就成操蛋了
I mean, that'd be nuts.
我去
AlI right.
老爸这双关有水平
Quality dad joke.
先别下结论哈
Before you say anything,
我没在刷约会软件 在看视频
this is not a dating app. It's a video.
这个宝宝坐在雪地里
It's the one with the baby sitting in the snow going...
是的 那个视频超逗
Yeah, that's a good one.
知道吗 我该向你道个歉
Hey, you know what? I owe you an apology.
是我太小题大做了
Yeah, I made way too big a deal
一个无伤大雅的小软件而已
about you being on a silly little app,
你如果再装回来
and, uh, I wouldn't blame you
我也不会怪你的
for putting it back on your phone.
不用 我不需要了
Nah, I don't need it.
我都忘记它存在了
I forgot it was even there.
不是 但是真的
No, but really, really,
你应该把它装回去
you should put it back.
你懂的 哪怕是向我宣誓 我没有
You know, if only to show me I had no right
让你删掉它的权利
telling you to delete it, huh?
我以为自己是谁啊
Who the hell do I think I am?
所以你想让我重新刷探探吗
So you want me to start using it again?
我也没说你一定要刷
Well, I'm not saying you have to use it
但我不能删对吗
But Ishould have it?
你有不删的
You should have the right
权利
to have it.
好 我们在一起有八个月了吧
Okay, we ve been together, what, eight months?
我好像终于有点
I think I'm finally starting
看懂你了
to understand you. Okay.
还记得我让你向学校上报
Remember when you made us register our relationship
我们的关系吗 你一直坚称
at the school, but you kept insisting
咱俩只是“暧昧”
that we call it a"vibe"?
-暧昧的意思是有感觉  -是
Well, vibe means we vibing. It's...Yeah.
是 马尔科姆 我们是有感觉
Yeah, Malcolm, we're vibing,
一起很开心 很放松 很享受
we're hanging, we're chilling, we're kicking it.
是 我只是觉不出来咱们在谈恋爱
Yeah I just don't think we're dating.
是这样的
Well, you know,
我没不该往自己身上贴标签对不对
we shouldn't have to put labels on ourselves, right?
我们不是那种会给自己贴标签的人
We aren't label people.
还记得我把牙膏落你家
Remember the time I left my toothbrush at your place,
不小心落的 结果你直接抓狂的那次吗
accidentally, and you lost your mind?
我认为我那不叫抓狂
Okay, I would not say I lost my mind.
你直接带着它开去我家了
You drove it to my house.
现在我应你要求
And now that I've deleted the stupid app,
把这破应用删了
per your request,
你却怕了
you're scared
因为这就代表我俩在认真谈恋爱了
because that means we're in a real relationship.
你想亨受男友特权
You want boyfriend privileges,
却不想做人男朋友
but you don't want to be a boyfriend.
我可没时间陪你耗
And I don't have time for that.
好吧好吧 听着 珍妮尔
Okay. Okay, okay, look, Janelle,
我有解决办法了 好吗
I got the solution, okay?
别把探探下回手机了
Don't put Tinder back on your phone.
不 马尔科姆 我也有解决办法
No, Malcolm, I have the solution.
我们结束了
We're done.
什么 结束
What, done?
你是说 彻底玩完儿吗
You mean, like"done"done?
你愿意怎么理解都可以
You can say"done"as many times as you want.
结束了
It's over.
保重 马尔科姆
Take care of yourself, Malcolm.
等等 珍妮尔
Wait, Janelle
后来 不知为何 她就跟我分手了
And then, out of the blue, she broke up with me.
-敢信吗  -不
Can you believe that? No.
我们还以为你会
We thought you were going to
跟她提分手
break up with her. Mm- hmm.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
拜托 兄弟
Come on, man.
感觉这就是你的出路
This seemed like it was your way out.
经典的马尔科姆作风
It's vintage Malcolm.
你跟她们约会一段时间
You date them for a while,
发现有不对 然后就抽身出来了
you find something wrong, and then you're out
什么 我才没有
What? Man, I don't do that.
是嘛 凯莎
Oh, really? Keisha?
她第二根脚趾比大脚趾长
Her second toe was longer than her big toe.
你就不谈了
You were out.
我更倾向于
Well, I am drawn to
传统的人字拖审美
a more traditional flip- flop aesthetic.
塔尼亚不铺床
Tanya didn't make the bed.
她是最后一个出被窝的 所有人都知道这是规矩
She was the last one in it. Everyone knows that's the rule.
斯蒂芬妮 你就因为人家
Stephanie, You broke up with her
有自己的保龄球就跟她分手了
because she owned her own bowling ball.
很怪好吧 球场本来就提供的 特雷
It's weird. They have them at the alley, Trey.
是这样 我不想这么说 但是
Look, man, I hate to say it, but
你不大敢跟人安定下来
you have a commitment problem.
净胡扯
Man, you guys are crazy.
行吧 那你为什么不跟珍妮尔定下来呢
Okay, so why couldn't you commit to Janelle?
我本来打算确认关系的
I was planning on committing.
只是还没决定要不要做
I just hadn't decided to definitely do it yet.
哥 我不知道你想找什么样的
Brother, I don't know what you're looking for,
但珍妮尔很优秀
but Janelle was brilliant
还风趣
and funny,
而且她超喜欢你的
and she was super into you.
此话属实
He ain't lying.
如果我有个珍妮尔这样的可人儿
If I had a Janelle,
才不会上探探呢
I wouldn't even be on Tinder.
不会这么经常上
As much.
行吧 你知道吗 你们都说
Okay, you know what? Y'all are acting like
珍妮尔是完美的
Janelle is perfect,
可她 有缺点的
but she she has flaws.
比如说
Like what?
她从没看过
She has never seen
《美国之旅》
Coming to America.
行吧
Yeah, okay.
前几天 我说“性感巧克力”
Other day, I said, Sexual Chocolate. "
她都不知道我在说什么
She had no idea what I was talking about.
性感巧克力
Sexual Chocolate!
我有问题 对不对
I have a problem, don't I?
我都不知该怎么谢谢
I can't thank you enough
你的慷慨的礼物 凯蒂博士
for your generous gift, Dr. Kittay.
是 泳池见
Yes, see you at the pool.
穿速干泳裤
Oh, in a speedo?
你太幽默了
Oh, you're great.
嘿 珍玛
Hey, Gemma.
我们得好好谈谈
we got to have a real talk.
我是代表老师们来的
I am here on behalf of the teachers.
礼品袋是让他们很开心吗
Oh, did the gift bags cheer them up?
其实 那东西搞得老师们更生气了
Well, actually, they made the teachers slightly angrier.
你看啊 我们都有蜡烛
You see, we all have candles,
但我们需要的是帮手
but what we need is help.
我们人手不足
We're understaffed.
大家需要助教
We need teachers'aides.
我非常明白你意思
I so hear you,
而且我已经跟董事会讨论过了
and I've discussed it with the board...Uh- huh.
只是现在没有这个预算
...and it's just not in the budget right now.
但有预算建泳池
But a swimming pool is in the budget?
我倒希望有呢 所以我们才办了筹款活动呀
I wish. That's why we're having a fundraiser.
那你为什么不为招助教
So why don't you have a fundraiser
办个筹款活动呢
for teachers'aides?
招助教不是这样的
That's not how it works.
你可以让它变成这样啊
Until you make it work that way.
蒂娜 我要面对的是
Tina, there's a whole board of trustees
一整个董事会 抱歉
I have to answer to. Im sorry.
但是 嘿
But, hey,
如果你有任何需要 直说就是
if there's anything you need, just name it.
我一直在说呀 珍玛
I've been naming it, Gemma.
助教
Teachers aides.
抱歉 我得接一下
I'm sorry, I've got to take this.
谢弗先生 你好
Mr. Schaefer, hello.
不不不 一点都不忙
No, no, no, Im not busy at all.
要知道 你永远不知道
You know you never know
膝盖的重要性
how important a knee is
直到
until you
一边膝盖没法用
you don't have one, you know?
我上个月掉地上的东西现在还躺那儿呢
Anything I dropped on the ground this last month stayed there.
所以你现在好受多了哈
So, you feel better now, huh?
嘿 我感觉好极了 这样
Hey, I feel great. You know what?
来防守我
Tackle me.
嘿 别勾搭我哈
Hey, don't tempt me.
嘿 二位 怎么样呀
Ooh, hey, guys. How's it going?
嘿 卡尔文 我找到你墨镜了
Oh, hey, Calvin, uh, I found your sunglasses.
你应该是给掉车道上了
I think you dropped them in the driveway.
要不这样 把眼镜扔地上
You know what? Drop them now.
扔了
Drop them.
好吧
Okay. Um
你兄弟德里克把我整好了
Your man Derek here got me straight, man.
没有戴夫我做不到的
Well, I couldn't have done it without Dave.
戴夫
Dave?
戴夫做了什么
What'd Dave do?
我需要激励你更加努力
Look, I needed to inspire you to try harder.
所以
DAVE: So, uh,
德里克把我捧成了
Derek held me up as an example
力量和男子气概的典范
of strength and machismo.
我利用戴夫来点燃
You see, I used Dave here to light
你心中的竞争之火
that competitive fire in you.
你我这样的运动员
You know, athletes like you and me,
所需要的只是被人挑战
we just need to be challenged.
是是是
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
是 我们是一样的
You know. Yeah, we're the same,
你知道吧
you know?
所以你的意思是
So- so, what you're saying is that Dave
戴夫治疗中没有那么硬汉
wasn't so tough in his sessions?
没 他哭的像个宝宝
No. He cried like a baby.
我们宣传册上有模型
We've got the mockups on the brochure.
水上中心看起来很棒
The aquatic center looks great.
是 我看到温度计了
Yes, I have seen the thermometer.
不 我不知道谁千的
No, I have no idea who did it.
我们不需要臭水池
We don't need no stinking pool.
老师们在学校需要有人帮持
Teachers need some help at school.
-我们不需要臭水池  -我该挂了
We don't need no stinking pool. I've got to run.
老师们在学校需要有人帮持
Teachers need some help at school.
我们不需要臭水池
We don't need no stinking pool.
老师们在学校需要有人帮持
Teachers need some help at school.
蒂娜 不是吧
Tina, really?
我们不要校长约翰逊
We don't want Principal Johnson.
让她打道回去威斯康辛
Send her back home to Wisconsin.
我们不要校长约翰逊
We don't want Principal Johnson.
让她打道回去威斯康辛
Uh...Send her back home to Wisconsin.
我是密歇根的
I'm from Michiganl
让她打道回去威斯康辛
Send her back home to Wisconsin.
蒂娜 跟他们说呀
Tina, tell theml
让她打道回去威斯康辛
Send her back home to Wisconsin.
我们不要校长约翰逊
We don't want Principal Johnson...
没有正义 就不做作业
GROVER: No justice, no homework.
No justice, no homework.
格罗弗 你干嘛呢 上课去
Grover, what are you doing? Get to class.
此处没有老师 珍玛
There are no teachers, Gemma.
他是盟友
Hels an ally.
校长没有原则
The principal has no principles
你这俩单词都拼错了 格罗弗
Both of those"principles are spelled wrong, Grover.
也许你的新泳池
Well, maybe your new swimming pool
能教会他区别
can teach him the difference.
你不需要用大喇叭的
You don't need the megaphone.
很容易就能听到你声音
You're very easy to hear.